hypedc.com 2014-06-03

# Legals - Free delivery, Hype DC

## Terms and Conditions

### Product Information

The website [www.hypedc.com](http://www.hypedc.com/) is owned and operated by Hype DC Pty Ltd. All products listed on [www.hypedc.com](http://www.hypedc.com/) are described to the best of our abilities and the specifications reflect the information that has been provided to us. All care is taken to ensure this information is correct, but we cannot eliminate the possibility of human error.

### Copyright

The description of our products and photography is the copyright property of Hype DC, and specifically you may not use that description as the description of the product should you choose to re-sell the items elsewhere. This includes all product information, images and specifications where applicable.

We have made every effort to display as accurately as possible the colours of our products that appear on the website. However, as the actual colours you see will depend on your monitor, we cannot guarantee that your monitor's display of any colour will accurately reflect the colour of the product on delivery.

All sizes and measurements are approximate, however we do make every effort to ensure they are as accurate as possible. Unless otherwise stated all sizes are in US, with anything unisex running in Mens US sizing.

Goods are subject to availability. As there is a delay between the time when the order is placed and the time when the order is accepted, the stock levels of each shoe may change. If an item you have ordered becomes out of stock before we accept the order we shall notify you as soon as possible and you will not be charged for the out of stock items.

We continually update our online store. Occasionally we may run offers in our retail stores that don't appear online or vice versa.

### Payment Information

All orders are prepaid. When ordering, your credit card is charged when you place your order. All orders are in Australian dollars. We accept Visa and Mastercard cards only.

Please note that we do not store your credit card number on our servers.

If the card payment is declined by your issuer for any reason, we cannot hold goods against your order.

**Note:** We take credit card fraud very seriously (which we know you'll appreciate) so we may contact you to ascertain shipping and credit card details for verification purposes. We reserve the right to ask for scans of photo ID.

### Shipping Information

The cost of shipping is clearly indicated for each product ordered, and is included in the invoice total. Orders are generally processed and posted in two to three working days. Unfortunately, at some times, processing orders may take longer.

Special request orders which are shipped directly from suppliers or directly from another store will incur an extra Shipping and Handling charge.

Free shipping only applies to orders shipped within Australia. We currently ship to New Zealand, USA, and the UK, freight charges are automatically added at the checkout upon selection of your country.

### Shipping Errors

Hype DC uses TNT to deliver your products. Whilst we use quality carriers, the reality is that errors may occur. In the event of delivery errors, Hype DC will use all its efforts to ensure you receive your goods, receive a replacement or are refunded your purchase price.

### Warranties

Where applicable, the warranty offered for the products sold by Hype DC are the manufacturer's warranty.

Where there is no manufacturer's warranty available, Hype DC offers a warranty for the products, as specified in the product specifications.

Hype DC's warranty is limited to replacement of the item or refund of the purchase price, to be determined by us.

### Limitation Of Liabilities

Under no circumstances will Hype DC be liable for any direct, indirect, special, incidental, consequential, or other damages resulting from any product purchased from Hype DC, beyond the value of the item purchased, including, without limitation, any lost profits, business interruption, or loss of programs or information. Hype DC reserves the right to change any specification, design, model and or other information without notice.

### Returning Defective Merchandise

At Hype DC we are proud of our products and guarantee all our products as being as advertised. We will attempt to replace any defective merchandise (subject to stock availability) or refund you for any defective merchandise (including reasonable shipping costs) provided that:

  1. The return is pre-arranged with Hype DC. This can be done by e-mailing [info@hypedc.com](mailto:info@hypedc.com)
  2. the product is returned to us with proof of purchase within 14 days of the date of purchase;
  3. the product is in its original condition; and
  4. the product is not defective as a result of misuse.

Should there be any problems with defective product, please contact Hype DC first. All returns must be pre-arranged by emailing [webstore@hypedc.com](mailto:webstore@hypedc.com)

If you are not completely satisfied with your purchase, simply return the item or items to us in their unworn and in original condition in the box within 14 days of receipt.

We will issue you with a full refund back on the credit card that you used to make the purchase, or exchange the item, at your request (subject to stock availability).

Alternatively, you can exchange your purchase at any Hype DC retail store provided the items are unworn and in original condition in the box and be within 14 days of receipt.

We will not under any circumstances refund the cost of shipping the original product to you in the case of exchange or refund.

All returns must be pre-arranged by emailing [webstore@hypedc.com](mailto:webstore@hypedc.com)

### Prices and Promotions

Prices are as set out on the website and include GST at the current rate but exclusive of delivery charges. We reserve the right to alter prices at any time.

If we discover an error in the price or description of an item you have ordered (it happens!), we may cancel your order at any time up to the point we send the item(s) to you. We will contact you where we become aware of an error and ask you whether you wish to continue with your order at the correct price or cancel it. If we do cancel your order you will receive a full refund of any charges paid in advance.

We continually update our online store. From time to time our retail stores may run special local promotions (which may not be available on our website) or we may offer special promotions online that are not available in the retail stores. For these reasons you may sometimes find that products on our Web site are priced differently to those in our stores. Some website promotions may not be available to customers in particular jurisdictions.

### General

Hype DC may revise these terms at any time. Use of this website is subject to the revised terms. These Terms were last revised in October 2013.

## Privacy

Hype DC Pty Ltd (ABN 16 081 432 313) has prepared this Privacy Statement to explain how it will handle the personal information of individuals who join to become HypeDC Members.

Your acceptance of this Privacy Statement is a condition of you becoming a HypeDC Member, and using the HypeDC website (at www.hypedc.com).

We shall accept your use of our website as your permission to collect and use information provided by you in accordance with this privacy statement.

### General privacy information

When you become a HypeDC Member, we ask you to provide us with a range of personal information. This includes your name and address, your email address, and other information such as current and previous address, telephone numbers and mobile phone numbers, bank account or credit card details, details of products purchased from us, details of your internet provider and browser and statistics on usage. Members must be 16 years or over. If a child is younger than 16, a parent or guardian must register on their behalf.

We collect this personal information so that we can provide you with regular product updates, as well as information about HypeDC's products, special offers and promotions. We use the personal information we collect to help us identify the HypeDC products and information that are most likely to be of interest to you. Also, your personal information may be used in order to research and develop our products and services, gain an understanding of our customers and their needs to provide a better service, conduct appropriate checks for credit-worthiness and fraud.

Email is the main method that we will use to contact you. When you become a HypeDC Member, we understand that you consent to receiving emails from us. From time to time, we may also send you special offers in the mail.

If you no longer wish to receive emails or other promotional materials from us or if you no longer accept this HypeDC Privacy Statement you can contact us (using the contact details below) and we will remove you from our mailing list.

We will store your personal information securely, and we will not sell your personal information to third parties. If you want to access your personal information, you can do so by contacting HypeDC Pty Ltd (using the contact details below). However, please note that the only personal information we will hold about you will be personal information that you provide to us. For the purposes set out in this policy statement, we may disclose your personal information to organisations outside of HypeDC Pty Ltd. The organisations to which information may be disclosed may include:

  * government and regulatory and other organisations as required or authorised by law;
  * fraud investigation bureau;
  * credit providers for credit related purposes such as credit worthiness, credit rating or credit provisions;
  * organisations involved in the transfer/sale of all or part of our assets;
  * our related companies.

From time to time, HypeDC Pty Ltd will run competitions and promotions, including through its website. Entry into such competitions and taking advantage of such promotions will be subject to additional terms and conditions. These will be made known to you when details of the competitions and promotions are released.

When you visit our website we may send you a cookie. Cookies may be used in the following ways: 

  1. To help us recognise you as a unique visitor (just a number) when you return to our website
  2. To compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our site.

Two types of cookies may be used on this website, -session cookies, which are temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the site, and persistent cookies, which remain in the cookie file of your browser.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies.

### Contacting HypeDC Pty Ltd

You can contact HypeDC Pty Ltd:

  * By email: [info@hypedc.com](mailto:info@hypedc.com)
  * By letter: Level 6, 228 Pitt Street, Sydney NSW 2000

This Privacy Statement may be updated from time to time. The last update was in August 2012.
